Harriman, Tom Collection of Amalgamated Publications 6352 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Tom Harriman Collection of Amalgamated Publications
1923-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harriman, Tom
ACWA
ACTWU
6352 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Publications.
8026736
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 31, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/032 PUBS: ACTWU. International Affairs Department. Art Gundershiem Publications 5743 PUBS: ACWA. The Advance 6174 PUBS: New York State United Teachers (NYSUT). Publications. 6286 PUBS: Delia Gottlieb, Collector. Publications. 6351 PUBS: Maggie Block Collection of Needletrades Union Publications
8026736
- Illustrated Almanac; Midwest News; Advance; Textile Labor; Labor Unity (Box 1)
  - Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac 1923, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Author: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA)
    - Item 2: Amalgamated Illustrated Almanac 1924, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Midwest News, 1964-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Midwest Regional News, 1964-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Author: Midwest Regional Joint Board
      Notes: v.1 (1964:Oct.) - v.10:no.3 (1976:Nov.). Bound volume
  - Advance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Advance, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.62:no.1-8 (1976) Bound volume
  - Textile Labor and ACTWU Labor, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Textile Labor, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Author: Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA)
      Notes: v.37:no.1-5 (1976). Bound volume. Bound with ACTWU Labor v.62:no.9 (1976)
    - Item 2: ACTWU Labor, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Author: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU)
      Notes: v.62:no.9 (1976). Bound volume. Bound with Textile Labor v.37:no.1-5 (1976).
  - Labor Unity, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Labor Unity, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Notes: v.62:no.10 (1976) - v.63:no.12 (1977). Bound vloume
- Labor Unity (Box 2)
  - Labor Unity, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Copy 2.
    - Item 1: Labor Unity, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Notes: v.62:no.10 (1976) - v.63:no.12 (1977). Bound volume. Copy 2.
  - Labor Unity, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Labor Unity, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Notes: v.64 (1978)- v.65 (1979). Bound volume.
  - Labor Unity, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Labor Unity, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Notes: v.66 (1980) - v.67 (1981). Bound volume.